<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
	<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
		<MASTER_PAD_VERSION>2.01</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
		<MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>PADGen 2.0.1.22 http://www.padgen.org</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
		<MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
	</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
	<Company_Info>
		<Company_Name>AdSapient Inc.</Company_Name>
		<Address_1>Voronjanskogo Str., 7a–706</Address_1>
		<Address_2>220039 Minsk, Belarus</Address_2>
		<City_Town>Minsk</City_Town>
		<State_Province>Minsk</State_Province>
		<Zip_Postal_Code>220039</Zip_Postal_Code>
		<Country>Belarus</Country>
		<Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.adsapient.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
		<Contact_Info>
			<Author_First_Name>AdSapient Inc.</Author_First_Name>
			<Author_Last_Name>AdSapient Inc.</Author_Last_Name>
			<Author_Email>contact@adsapient.com</Author_Email>
			<Contact_First_Name>Vitaly</Contact_First_Name>
			<Contact_Last_Name>Sazanovich</Contact_Last_Name>
			<Contact_Email>vitaly@adsapient.com</Contact_Email>
		</Contact_Info>
		<Support_Info>
			<Sales_Email>sales@adsapient.com</Sales_Email>
			<Support_Email>support@adsapient.com</Support_Email>
			<General_Email>contact@adsapient.com</General_Email>
			<Sales_Phone>+375 17 2281257</Sales_Phone>
			<Support_Phone>+375 17 2281257</Support_Phone>
			<General_Phone>+375 17 2281257</General_Phone>
			<Fax_Phone>+375 17 2281258</Fax_Phone>
		</Support_Info>
	</Company_Info>
	<Program_Info>
		<Program_Name>AdSapient Banner Manager</Program_Name>
		<Program_Version>1.3</Program_Version>
		<Program_Release_Month>12</Program_Release_Month>
		<Program_Release_Day>01</Program_Release_Day>
		<Program_Release_Year>2004</Program_Release_Year>
		<Program_Cost_Dollars>300</Program_Cost_Dollars>
		<Program_Cost_Other_Code />
		<Program_Cost_Other />
		<Program_Type>Demo</Program_Type>
		<Program_Release_Status>Alpha</Program_Release_Status>
		<Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
		<Program_OS_Support>Windows2000,WinXP,Windows2003,Unix,Linux,OS/2,Mac OS X</Program_OS_Support>
		<Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
		<Program_Change_Info />
		<Program_Specific_Category />
		<Program_Category_Class>Servers::Other Server Applications</Program_Category_Class>
		<Program_Categories />
		<Program_System_Requirements>CPU 1Ghz,RAM 512 Mb </Program_System_Requirements>
		<Includes_JAVA_VM>N</Includes_JAVA_VM>
		<Includes_VB_Runtime>N</Includes_VB_Runtime>
		<Includes_DirectX>N</Includes_DirectX>
		<File_Info>
			<Filename_Versioned>adsapient13.exe</Filename_Versioned>
			<Filename_Previous>adsapient13.exe</Filename_Previous>
			<Filename_Generic>adsapient13.exe</Filename_Generic>
			<Filename_Long>adsapient13.exe</Filename_Long>
			<File_Size_Bytes>2000000</File_Size_Bytes>
			<File_Size_K>1953</File_Size_K>
			<File_Size_MB>1.91</File_Size_MB>
		</File_Info>
		<Expire_Info>
			<Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
			<Expire_Count>10</Expire_Count>
			<Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
			<Expire_Other_Info />
			<Expire_Month />
			<Expire_Day />
			<Expire_Year />
		</Expire_Info>
	</Program_Info>
	<Program_Descriptions>
		<English>
			<Keywords>ad network software, advertising agency software, ad management, adserver, ad server, ad serve, ad serving, ad delivery, banner software, desktop advertising, desktop advertising software, advertising delivery, banner exchange software, ad banners</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>AdSapient Banner Management Software</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>AdSapient Banner Management Software - Intelligency, Performance, Precision.</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>AdSapient Banner Manager provides a cost-effective solution for banner ad management. It allows to easily create and manage online advertising campaigns delivering creatives in the most efficient and smart way, using reach targeting options.         </Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>AdSapient Banner Manager provides a cost-effective solution for banner ad management. It allows to easily create and manage online advertising campaigns delivering creatives in the most efficient and smart way. The advanced audience targeting and reporting modules will help you to encrease campaigns' ROI greatly leaving both the advertiser and the publisher satisfied with the advertising results. </Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>AdSapient Banner Manager provides a cost-effective solution for banner ad management. It allows to easily create and manage online advertising campaigns delivering creatives in the most efficient and smart way. The advanced audience targeting and reporting modules will help you to encrease campaigns' ROI greatly leaving both the advertiser and the publisher satisfied with the advertising results. The audience targeting is conveniently divided different filters: geo, content, context, traffic, time, keyword, behavior. Reporting is visually presented in pie charts and bar charts. In-build anti-fraud mechanism prevents abuse in publishing and ad serving. Campaigns' self-adjustment mechanism allow the marketer to encrease campaign's ROI without  constantly changing the settings. Secure authorization and payment transactions modules provide for smooth and stable functioning of your ad network. Users can play different roles in the system: advertiser, publisher, advertiser+publisher, exchange participant, advertiser+exchange participant, account manager, guest which makes this system truely universal in terms of online advertising. 
Main features:
- multiuser ad management system with user-friendly web-based interface; 
- 3rd generation ad serving functionality includes advanced targeting and campaign setup;
- visualized reporting available for export in different formats;
- supports all media formats;
- advanced post click tracking;
- keyword/context/content/behaviour/traffic/time/geo/system/net targeting;
- transparent behavior targeting does not violating visitor privacy;
- reach campaign delivery scheduling options;
- advanced financials management (setting payment rates, automatic invoice compilation);
- all kinds of notifications on different events;
- various system roles: advertiser, publisher, exchange participant, account manager, guest, admin and combinations of them;
- revenue-oriented system design and logic.

</Char_Desc_2000>
		</English>
	</Program_Descriptions>
	<Web_Info>
		<Application_URLs>
			<Application_Info_URL>http://www.adsapient.com</Application_Info_URL>
			<Application_Order_URL>http://www.adsapient.com</Application_Order_URL>
			<Application_Screenshot_URL>http://adsapient.com/screenshot.gif</Application_Screenshot_URL>
			<Application_Icon_URL>http://adsapient.com/images/logo.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
			<Application_XML_File_URL>http://adsapient.com/adsapient.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
		</Application_URLs>
		<Download_URLs>
			<Primary_Download_URL>http://www.adsapient.com</Primary_Download_URL>
			<Secondary_Download_URL>http://www.adsapient.com</Secondary_Download_URL>
			<Additional_Download_URL_1 />
			<Additional_Download_URL_2 />
		</Download_URLs>
	</Web_Info>
	<Permissions>
		<Distribution_Permissions>Shareware Terms of Use

General

As part of our service, AdSapient Inc. agrees to provide freely downloadable evaluation versions of this software. AdSapient Inc. agrees to provide this service free of charge. Upon notice published by AdSapient Inc., AdSapient Inc. may amend or modify these Terms of Service at any time. You agree to use the service in accordance with the Terms of Service.

Copyright Notices

The product is owned by AdSapient. All rights in the product including License Agreement Number, copyrights, licensing rights, patents, trademarks, trade secrets, design rights, engineering rights, moral rights, and any other intellectual property rights belong to AdSapient. These rights are not transferred as part of this agreement.

No part of the product including the License Agreement may be reproduced, published, transmitted electronically, mechanically or otherwise, transcribed, stored in a retrieval system or translated into any language in any form, by any means, for any purpose other than the purchaser's personal use, without the express written permission of AdSapient.

End User License Agreement

This license agreement is a legal agreement between you the end user (either as an individual or an entity) and AdSapient Inc. The software and any of its supporting documentation and associated hardware are herein after referred to as the product .

By installing or using the product, you indicate your complete and unconditional acceptance of these terms and conditions. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this agreement promptly remove the product from your computer and destroy associated documentation.

Should there be any conflict between the terms and conditions of this agreement and the terms and conditions of any other agreement between you and AdSapient or their servants or agents in relation to the product the terms and conditions of this agreement shall apply.

If any provision of this agreement is found to be unlawful or void then that provision shall be severed from this agreement and will not affect the validity of the remaining provisions.

Information contained in the product is subject to change without notice and does not represent a commitment or contracted obligation on the part of AdSapient.

Evaluation License Agreement

This Evaluation License Agreement grants you a non-exclusive License to use the product for an evaluation period of fifteen (15) days from the date you install the product. On the sixteenth (16) day after you installed the product you must either register the product by means of purchasing a commercial License Agreement from AdSapient or destroy all copies of the product in your possession, and any related documentation.

You may make a single copy of the software only and no other part of the product in a machine readable form for backup use only.

This License Agreement (including the product) is not transferable. You may not lend, loan, lease, rent, sell or distribute the product (or copies) in any form.

Limitations of Use

You are expressly forbidden from making alterations or modifications to, merge, adapt, de-compile, disassemble, reverse engineer, or attempt to discover the source code without the expressed written permission from AdSapient. You are expressly forbidden from using any part of the product in life saving or life critical applications without the expressed written permission from AdSapient.

Limitations of Liability

Under no circumstances, including, but not limited to, negligence, shall AdSapient Inc., its subsidiary and parent companies or affiliates be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special or consequential damages that result from the use of, or the inability to use, AdSapient Inc. services. If you are dissatisfied with any remotely hosted AdSapient's services, or with any of AdSapient Inc. terms and conditions, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using AdSapient Inc. services. In addition, You release AdSapient Inc. and its affiliates from any damages that you incur, and agree not to assert any claims against them, arising from your use of it's products or services.</Distribution_Permissions>
		<EULA />
	</Permissions>
	<ASP>
		<ASP_FORM>Y</ASP_FORM>
		<ASP_Member>N</ASP_Member>
		<ASP_Member_Number />
	</ASP>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
